export const Questions=[
    {
prompt:"What is 1+3",
optionA:'24',
optionB:'21',
optionC:'4',
optionD:'2',
answer:'optionC'

    },
    {
        prompt:" which is a streaming platform?",
        optionA:"Twitter",
        optionB:"Twitch",
        optionC:"Google",
        optionD:"Robinhood",
        answer:'optionB'

    },
    {
        prompt:"Which of the following is used in React.js to increase the performance?",
        optionA:"Original DOM",
        optionB:"Virtual DOM",
        optionC:"Both A and B",
        optionD:"None of the above",
        answer:'optionB'

    },
    {
        prompt:"Which of the following act as the input of a class-based component?",
        optionA:"Class",
        optionB:"Render",
        optionC:"Factory",
        optionD:"Props",
        answer:'optionD'

    },
    {
        prompt:"How many numbers of elements a valid react component can return?",
        optionA:"1",
        optionB:"2",
        optionC:"4",
        optionD:"5",
        answer:'optionA'

    },
    {
        prompt:"What is the default port where webpack-server runs?",
        optionA:"3000",
        optionB:"8080",
        optionC:"3030",
        optionD:"6060",
        answer:'optionB'

    },
    {
        prompt:"How many ways of defining your variables in ES6?",
        optionA:"1",
        optionB:"3",
        optionC:"4",
        optionD:"5",
        answer:'optionB'

    },
    {
        prompt:"What are the two ways to handle data in React?",
        optionA:"State and Props",
        optionB:"Services & Components",
        optionC:"State & Services",
        optionD:"State & Component",
        answer:'optionA'

    },
    {
        prompt:"Which of the following is used to pass data to a component from outside in React.js?",
        optionA:"SetState",
        optionB:"Render with argumentns",
        optionC:"Props",
        optionD:"Prototypes",
        answer:'optionC'

    },
    {
        prompt:" What does ES6 stand for?",
        optionA:"ECMAScript 6",
        optionB:"ECMA 6",
        optionC:"ECMAJavaScript 6",
        optionD:"EJavaScript 6",
        answer:'optionA'

    },




];